Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Slavic Languages, 1969-1983 (Box 157)
  - Russian, 1971-1983 (Box 157)
  - Sociology, 1981-1983 (Box 157)
  - Statistics and Memos, 1986 (Box 157)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 158)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes and Agendas, 1970-1971 (Box 158)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes and Agendas, 1969-1970 (Box 158)
  - Curriculum Committee Proposals, 1965-1969 (Box 158)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, Agendas and Notes, 1962-1968 (Box 158)
  - Curriculum Committee Notices, Agenda and Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 159)
  - Curriculum Committee Actions Taken by the UFCAS, 1983-1984 (Box 159)
  - Curriculum Agendas and Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 159)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, Agenda and Notes, 1973-1978 (Box 159)
  - Dean Flowers-Dr. Cleaveland, Mr. Sanford, 1974 (Box 159)
  - HC 80.01, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.02, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.03, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.04, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.05, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.06, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.07, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.08, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.09, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.10, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.11, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.12, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.13, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.14, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.15, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.16, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.17, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.18, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.19, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.20, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.21, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.22, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.23, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.24, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.25, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.26, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.27, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.28, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.29, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC Grade Sheets, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC List and Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC Field Trip/Policy, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC BFAC, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.01, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.02, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.03, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.04, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.05, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.06, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.07, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.08, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.09, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.10, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.11, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC Healthcare cancelled, 2000 (Box 160)
  - HC Class Lists, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.01, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.02, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.03, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.04, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.05, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.06, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.07, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.08, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.09, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.10, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.11, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.12, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.13, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.14, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.15, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.16, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.17, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.18, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.19, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.20, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.21, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.22, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.23, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.24, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.25, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.26, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.27, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 80.28, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC Inspiration, not approved, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.01, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.02, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.03, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.04, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.05, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.06, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.07, 2001 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.01, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.02, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.03, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.04, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.05, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.06, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.07, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.08, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.09, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.10, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.11, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.12, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.13, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.14, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.15, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.16, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.17, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.18, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.19, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.20, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.21, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.22, 2002 (Box 160)
  - HC 79.23, 2002 (Box 160)
  - Billings, Dwight, 1987-1994 (Box 161)
  - Cole, R. Taylor, 1975-1991 (Box 161)
  - Diamond, Irving, 1993-1994 (Box 161)
  - Fish, Stanley, 1988-1990 (Box 161)
  - Fowlie, Wallace, 1992-1995 (Box 161)
  - Griffiths, Phillip, 1984-1987 (Box 161)
  - Havighurst, C., 1987-1989 (Box 161)
  - Langford, Thomas, 1986-1994 (Box 161)
  - Mudimbe, Valentin, 1991-1996 (Box 161)
  - Purves, Dale, 1992-1993 (Box 161)
  - Williams, Peter, 1987-1989 (Box 161)
  - DPC Administration and History, 1975-1986 (Box 161)
  - DPC Advertising Old, 1985-1986 (Box 161)
  - DPC BIPS Info, Admissions, 1995 (Box 161)
  - DPC Declined Invitations, 1981-1986 (Box 161)
  - DPC Distribution Info, 1996 (Box 161)
  - DPC Flyers, 1991 (Box 161)
  - DPC Flyers: Samples, 1998-1999 (Box 161)
  - DPC Form Letters, 1996 (Box 161)
  - DPC Historical, 1978-1988 (Box 161)
  - DPC Miscellaneous, 1987-1992 (Box 161)
  - DPC Publicity Flyer to be done, 1998 (Box 161)
  - DPC Responds to Crs. Designations, 1987 (Box 161)
  - DPC Statistics, 1991-1996 (Box 161)
  - DPC Teacher/Course Evaluation Form, 1994 (Box 161)
  - DPC, 1992-1998 (Box 161)
  - Publicity File/Holsti DPC 200S, 1999 (Box 162)
  - DPC 207S Psychobiology, 1999 (Box 162)
  - DPC 196S Human Population Growth, 1999 (Box 162)
  - DPC 185S Ethics and Issues, 1999 (Box 162)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Flyer Distribution, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Labels Copies, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Print Out, for Registrar's Office, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Publicity File: Flyers, 2000 (Box 162)
  - DPC 183S Science and Religion, 2000 (Box 162)
  - DPC 207S Psychobiology, 2000 (Box 162)
  - DPC 196S Human Population Growth, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Pagan World, Duke in Florence Program, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 162)
  - Flyers, 2001 (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 162)
  - Publicity/Chronicle Expenses, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 200S Democracy, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 184S Ethical Issues, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 191 Research Independent Study, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 202S Remembrance/Reconciliation, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 190S Pagan World Divine Comedy (Box 162)
  - DPC Fall 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 183S Science and Religion, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 207S Psychobiology, 2001 (Box 162)
  - DPC 200S.11 Democracy, 2002 (Box 162)
  - DPC 190S Pagan World, 2002 (Box 162)
  - DPC 183S Science and Religion, 2002 (Box 162)
  - DPC 193S Gender, Politics and Higher Ed, 2002 (Box 162)
  - DPC 207S Psychobiology, 2002 (Box 162)
  - DPC 185 Ethical Issues, 2003 (Box 162)
  - DPC 200S Democracy, 2003 (Box 162)
  - Course Committee Approved Courses not in Bulletin, 1974-1985 (Box 162)
  - Requests not Approved, 1983-1984 (Box 162)
  - University Writing Courses, 1985 (Box 162)
  - Zoology, 1970-1985 (Box 162)
  - Sirena WuDunn Scholarship, 1985-1988 (Box 162)
  - Sirena WuDunn Scholarship List, 1994-1997 (Box 162)
  - Sirena WuDunn Scholarship Financial Matters, 1990-1995 (Box 162)
  - Sirena WuDunn Scholarship, 1990-1999 (Box 162)
  - Janet Chiang Awards, 2002-2003 (Box 162)
  - Janet B. Chiang Memorial Grant Winners List, 1995 (Box 162)
  - Janet B. Chiang Memorial Grant, 1992-1997, 2001 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Manual with Charters, 1975-1989 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Current List of Winners, 1991-1995 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Scholarships Listings, 1987-1988 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Misc. Correspondence, 1994 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Misc. Scholarships, undated (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Appointments, Reports, etc., 1979-1988 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee: Financial Info., 1988 (Box 162)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 162)
  - Historical House Course Info., 1969-2001 (Box 162)
  - HC Evaluations, 2001-2002 (Box 162)
  - HC Not Approved, 1997 (Box 162)
  - HC Azucar Salsa, 1998 (Box 162)
  - HC American Sign Language, 1999 (Box 162)
  - HC Ethics and Peer Education, 1999 (Box 162)
  - HC Legal Rights, withdrawn, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Documentary Photograph, not approved, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Hurricanes, not approved, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Transitions, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Welfare, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Website Brief Descriptions, 1999, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Lists and Display Ads, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC not accepted, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC Enrollment, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC withdrawn, 2000 (Box 162)
  - HC issues to be resolved, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Course Synopsis Handbooks, 1988 Spring-1990 Spring (Box 163)
  - Course Synopsis Handbooks, 1990 Fall-1993 Fall (Box 164)
  - Course Synopsis Handbooks, 1993 Spring-1995 Spring (Box 165)
  - Course Synopsis Handbooks, 1995 Spring-1997 Fall (Box 166)
  - Course Synopsis Handbooks, 1998 Spring (Box 167)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Naval and Air Force ROTC's, 1960 (Box 168)
  - AFROTC Advisory Panel, 1954-1955 (Box 168)
  - AFROTC Color Presentation, 1954 (Box 168)
  - AFROTC Contract, 1951 (Box 168)
  - AFROTC Contract Revision, 1958 (Box 168)
  - Air Force ROTC, 1949-1958 (Box 168)
  - Air Science, 1959-1963 (Box 168)
  - Armory, 1960-1961 (Box 168)
  - Department of Defense Directive No. 800.06-1: Policies relating to ROTC Affairs, 1951 (Box 168)
  - Duke University-ROTC, 1953-1964 (Box 168)
  - M-Day Plans, 1950-1959 (Box 168)
  - Military Information, 1950-1954 (Box 168)
  - Naval Engineering Training Program, 1956 (Box 168)
  - Naval Science, 1951-1964 (Box 168)
  - NROTC Dis-enrollments - RESTRICTED, 1953-1955 (Box 168)
  - NROTC Organization and Regulations Manual, 1957 (Box 168)
  - NROTC State Selection Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 168)
  - Public Law 550, 1952 (Box 168)
  - ROTC Conference-Minnesota, 1962 (Box 168)
  - ROTC Units- Material Common to Both, 1953 (Box 168)
  - War Emergency-Committee on Undergraduate Counseling on Military Service, 1951 (Box 168)
  - War Emergency-Letters and Replies, 1950-1951 (Box 168)
  - War Emergency-USMT, Universal Military Service and Training, 1951-1952 (Box 168)
  - War Projects, 1951 (Box 168)
  - House Course: Race and Education, 1993-1994 (2 folders) (Box 169)
  - Audiocassette tapes of speakers: Use copies must be made for patron use. Of the speakers listed below, only 5 offered written permission for their remarks to be taped and used. The paperwork is included in the folders mentioned above.
    - Race, Education, and Business, with Kenneth M. Chestnut, 1993 Oct. 27 (Permission Granted) (Box 169)
    - Race, Education, and Images in the Media, with Dr. Chuck Stone, 1993 Sept. 27. (Permission Granted) (Box 169)
    - Race, Education, and the Arts, with Dr. Murry N. DePillars, 1993 Oct. 6 (Permission Granted) (Box 169)
    - Race, Education, and the New Civil Rights, with Professor Lani Guinier, 1993 Dec. 9 (Permission Granted) (Box 169)
    - Race, Education, and Religion, with Chaplain (Major General) Matthew A. Zimmerman, 1993 Oct. 13 (Permission Granted) (Box 169)
    - The Impact of Race and Education on Economics and Politics, with Rev. Dr. Benjamin Chavis, Jr., 1993 Nov. 10 (RESTRICTED - PERMISSION NOT RECEIVED) (Box 169)
  - Files on University Program in Human Development, 1983-1985 (8 folders) (Box 170)
  - Undergraduate Exchange Program: Duke/Howard Exchange Agreement, 1980 (Box 170)
  - Undergraduate Exchange Program: Spelman Exchange, 2003-2004 (Box 170)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted until 2029.
  - Undergraduate Exchange Program: Exchange Programs, Undergraduate, 1980-2001 (Box 170)
    Restricted until 2026.
  - Undergraduate Exchange Program: Howard Exchange, 2001, 2004 (Box 170)
  - Undergraduate Exchange Program: Duke/Howard Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 170)
  - AAC&U Application, 2000; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Greater Expectations: AAC&U Consortium on College Education, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Curriculum 2000 Analysis, 2004; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Untitled Binder, 1999-2008; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Report of the Lang. Task Force, 1998 (Box 170)
  - Curriculum Report Trinity College: Background Material, 1980-1997; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Writing Program, University, Task Force, 1995-2015 (Box 170)
  - University Writing Program: Visits and Reports, 1998 (Box 170)
  - Writing Program Cornell Workshop, John S. Knight Wrt Pro, 1998-1999 (Box 170)
  - Writing Program Material (Thompson), 1997; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Academic Advising, 2004-2007 (Box 170)
  - Outcome Assessment, undated; 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Liberal Education, 2014 (Box 171)
  - University Projects, 2003-2008; 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Academic Support Services, 2007 (Box 171)
  - Undergraduate Research, 2004-2006 (Box 171)
  - Undergraduate and Interdisciplinary Education, undated (Box 171)
  - Writing, 1999-2005; 3 folders (Box 171)
  - Duke Faculty Associates Annual Report, 1996 (Box 171)
  - Enhancing Undergraduate Education, 1998-2002; 3 folders (Box 171)
- Accession UA2019.0064, 1968-2006; 2
  For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
  Materials have not been screened for sensitive or restricted content. Staff will need to screen materials before use. Please contact Research Services for more information.
  - Curriculum Committee Reports (Box 172)
  - Curriculum Committee On Diversity Report (Box 172)
  - Language Task Force Report (Box 172)
  - Natural Sciences Task Force Report (Box 172)
  - Structure and Choice In A Liberal Education, 1986 (Box 172)
  - Varieties Of Learning Experience c. 2, 1968 (Box 172)
  - EW's Copy Of Wardropper Comm. Report (Ad Hoc Comm.) and Summary Of Fate Of Its Recs (Box 172)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 172)
  - Wardropper Proposal: Model 4 Year Programs (Box 172)
  - Writing Task Force Report (Box 172)
  - Staff, 2001-2002 (Box 172)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 173)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 173)
  - From Files Of C. Young and K. Rigsby, 1986-1988 (Box 173)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 173)
  - Outline Of Curriculum Changes At Duke Since 1969 (Box 173)
  - Curriculum 2000 Review Committee Report (Nowicki) (Box 173)
  - Mails Re: Curriculum Revision Code Changes (Box 173)
  - Curric. 2000 Final Report (Approved By Council) (Box 173)
  - Reports, 1970s-1990s; 2 folders (Box 173)
  - Curriculum Review Report, 1974 (Partin) (Box 173)
  - Stats On Majors Reqs Sp06, 2006 (Box 174)
  - COFHE/Econ Responses (Ruderman) (Box 174)
  - Economics Cc 2 Of 2 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, Spring 2006 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, Fall 2005 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee: Committee Actions, 2004-2005 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee: Chair Report To Exec. Comm, 2004-2005 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2005 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2004 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee: Past Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 174)
  - Committee On Curriculum, 2000-2001 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 174)
  - Certificate Review 1997-98 (P. Fish, Chr. Curric. Comm.), 1997-1998 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 174)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1997 (Box 175)
  - Revision Of Certificate Programs (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee Report, 1996-1997 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Matters Outside Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1996 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1995 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1994 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1995 (Box 175)
  - Nomenclature Statement (Box 175)
  - (O'Barr) Curriculum Review Committee Report, 1993 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 175)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 175)
  - Staff, 2002-2003 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 2003-2004 (Box 176)
  - Staff Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 1996-1997 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 1995-1996 (Box 176)
  - Dean's Staff, 1994-1995 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 1993-1994 (Box 176)
  - Staff Work (Box 176)
  - Staff, 2004-2005 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 2000-2001 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 1999-2000 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 1997-1998 (Box 176)
  - Staff, 2006-2007 (Box 176)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 176)
  - Procedures Manual (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1975 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1976 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1976 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 177)
  - Staff Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 177)
  - Staff Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 177)
  - Staff Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 177)
  - Unlabeled Folders, 2 folders (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1982-1983 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 177)
  - Briefing Report (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1985-1986 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1986-1987 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1987-1988 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1988-1989 (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff (with Unlabelled Folder), 1989-1990 (Box 177)
  - Visiting, Special, Guest Student (Box 177)
  - Dean's Staff, 1990-1991 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1991-1992 (Box 177)
  - Staff, 1998-1999 (Box 177)